<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jon Chua</title>
    <link>https://jonchua.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jon Chua</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jonchua.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Demo</title>
      <link>https://jonchua.dev/posts/theme-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonchua.dev/posts/theme-demo/</guid>
      <description>Style Demo h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Deleted text
This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1$ and with math blocks:
$$ \sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1 $$
   Heading Another heading     text text   text text   text text     Block quotes are written like so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jonchua.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonchua.dev/about/</guid>
      <description> About Me Modules Taken in NUS School of Computing 2019 / 2020 Semester 1 (Planned)  CS2101: Effective Communication for Computing Professionals CS2103T: Software Engineering CS2106: Introduction to Operating Systems CS2107: Introduction to Information Security ST2334: Probability and Statistics GEH1036: Living with Mathematics  Teaching Assistant (TA) Roles
 CS2040: Data Structures and Algorithms CS1101S: Programming Methodology CS1010E: Programming Methodology  2018 / 2019 Summer  Orbital 2019: Project Gemini Source Academy Summer Programme: Frontend Testing Team Freshmen Orientation Week (FOW) 2019: Prologs Member  2018 / 2019 Semester 2  CS1010R: Programming Methodology CS2030: Programming Methodology II CS2040: Data Structures and Algorithms CS2100: Computer Organization IS1103: IS Innovations in Organisations and Society GER1000: Quantitative Reasoning GEQ1000: Asking Questions GES1021: Natural Heritage of Singapore  2018 / 2019 Semester 1  CS1101S: Programming Methodology CS1231: Discrete Structures MA1101R: Linear Algebra I MA1521: Calculus for Computing GET1020: Darwin and Evolution  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jonchua.dev/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonchua.dev/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Feel free to contact me at </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jonchua.dev/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonchua.dev/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>Portfolio Hack&amp;amp;Roll 2019: NUS Exams Countdown A simple exam countdown app for Hack&amp;amp;Roll 2019, my first hackathon.
 Github Repo Devpost Submission
Todo List I created a simple todo list in Ruby on Rails as a CVWO (Computing for Voluntary Welfare Organisations) Assignment.
 Github Repo Heroku Deployment</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>